/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data6_3', {
    title: '6.3 Equivalent Fractions',
    path: '6.3-equivalent-fractions  ',
    children: [{ //----1
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Are these fractions equivalent?}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{12}}}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Yes}{T}}{\\but{No}{F}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{4 · 12\xA0 = \xA08 · 6<br><br>}}{\\html{\xA0 48\xA0 = \xA048}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----2
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Are these fractions equivalent?}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{14}}{\\str{16}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{20}}{\\str{35}}}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Yes}{F}}{\\but{No}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{14 · 35\xA0 \u2260 \xA020 · 16<br><br>}}{\\html{490\xA0 \u2260 \xA0320}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----3
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Are these fractions equivalent?}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{14}}{\\str{16}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{16}}{\\str{36}}}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Yes}{F}}{\\but{No}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{14 · 36\xA0 \u2260 \xA016 · 16<br><br>}}{\\html{504\xA0 \u2260 \xA0256}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----4
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Are these fractions equivalent?}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{9}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{15}}}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Yes}{T}}{\\but{No}{F}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{6 · 15\xA0 = \xA010 · 9<br><br>}}{\\html{90\xA0 = \xA090}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----5
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Are these fractions equivalent?}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{18}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{20}}}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Yes}{F}}{\\but{No}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{15 · 20\xA0 \u2260 \xA08 · 18<br><br>}}{\\html{\xA0 300\xA0 \u2260 \xA0144}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----6
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Solve for the missing number.}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{X}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\str{X \xA0= \xA0}}{\\input{30}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{3 · X\xA0 = \xA06 · 15<br><br>}}{\\html{3 · X\xA0 = \xA0 90<br><br>}}{\\html{X\xA0 = \xA0 90 \xA0 \xF7 \xA03<br><br>}}{\\html{X\xA0 = \xA030}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----7
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Solve for the missing number.}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{76}}{\\str{X}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{19}}{\\str{21}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\str{X \xA0= \xA0}}{\\input{84}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{76 · 21\xA0 = \xA0X · 19<br><br>}}{\\html{ 1596 \xA0  = \xA0X · 19<br><br>}}{\\html{ 1596 \xA0 \xF7 \xA019 = X<br><br>}}{\\html{84\xA0 = \xA0X}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----8
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Solve for the missing number.}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{27}}{\\str{26}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{X}}{\\str{104}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\str{X \xA0= \xA0}}{\\input{108}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{\xA0 27 · 104\xA0 = \xA026 · X<br><br>}}{\\html{\xA0 2808 \xA0 = \xA026 · X<br><br>}}{\\html{ 2808  \xA0 \xF7 \xA026 =\xA0X<br><br>}}{\\html{\xA0 108\xA0 = \xA0X}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----9
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Solve for the missing number.}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{25}}{\\str{45}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{75}}{\\str{X}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\str{X \xA0= \xA0}}{\\input{135}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{25 · X\xA0 = \xA045 · 75<br><br>}}{\\html{25 · X\xA0 = \xA0 3375 <br><br>}}{\\html{X\xA0 = \xA0 3375 \xA0 \xF7 \xA025<br><br>}}{\\html{X\xA0 = \xA0135}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, { //----10
        title: 'Equivalent Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\str{Solve for the missing number.}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{19}}{\\str{38}}}{\\sign{=}}{\\frac{\\str{X}}{\\str{152}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\str{X \xA0= \xA0}}{\\input{76}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\html{19 · 152\xA0 = \xA038 · X<br><br>}}{\\html{ 2888 \xA0 = \xA038 · X<br><br>}}{\\html{ 2888 \xA0 \xF7 \xA038\xA0 = \xA0X<br><br>}}{\\html{\xA0 76\xA0 = \xA0X}}}{center-tr-txt}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, ]
});
